There are so many interesting things in this world, you should
try them all.  It would be such a
shame to miss it.
Congratulations on the 6th anniversary of the original creator!  I'm
Itooka, playing the role of the uncle.  Has it really been six years already?
Six years means they'll be graduating from elementary school soon, right?
I am so incredibly happy to be a part of this long-running series
.  Continuing something for six years is a
difficult thing, so I really
feel that this is a work that is loved by each and every one of those travelers.   The
Johnny's girls are just so incredibly cute.   It's just
overflowing with cuteness.  Well, she
has an innocent cuteness, and also a kind of
prima donna-like
cuteness [musically].  Meanwhile, because his
older brother is made of water, he is in the shape of a person, and that's correct,
but sometimes he is in the shape of a person, and sometimes he is in the
shape of a mermaid, and he is
really cute and wonderful, so I would like anyone who hasn't seen him in action yet to definitely check him out.  The
slithery movement of the attacks during battle.   I hope the
relaxed and cute look came across.  It
moves in a really smooth way, but it also has a
cuteness that comes from being strong.   I don't know if it's right to
summarize this as "cute,"
but seriously, no matter how you
look at it, it's cute
, and [music] my hairstyle, or rather,
how should I put it.  I
really love the room accessories too, and there are flowers
attached to them like in Prima Donna [music], but today I really wanted to get
closer to Bojani Tour [music], so I had my hairstyle made to look like flowers, and
I just wanted to have the
cuteness of Bojani Tour
.
What kind of character? Well, what is it, really
?  Well, you see a lot of his usual bright Johnny's Tour
[music] expressions,
but when he talks about something a little deeper, he shows
expressions that you don't normally see, and I've
seen him in various roles as Mojanitsu,
but what I'd like to
see more of in the future is that
Bojanitsu is a prima donna, and he's a
boy who is always very confident in his singing voice and how he looks to others
.  However, there's a moment when this character
hits a wall [music]
, and I think she's a very hardworking character,
but even within that, there's a moment in
this story when she experiences setbacks and hits a wall
, and I'd like to play the role of her overcoming them together with the help of the traveler
.  thank you.
[Laughs]
Pojani Tour likes cold and
sweet things.  Well, I do
like ice cream, of course, but what
I'm really into this summer is shaved ice
.  So, I wonder if Johnny's tour members have ever had that
delicious, fluffy shaved ice made with real ice
? Do they have it at Sneijunaa
? If they haven't had it, I'd
love to give them that fluffy shaved ice topped with fluffy cream as a gift.
In the real world, uh, it's a technique that involves, well, water, a pretty
intense water attack,
[laughs] I wonder if that makes sense
? It's for use in the real world, after all
.  Well, it's been really
hot lately, so I'd
like to build my own original swimming pool.  [Music] We'll
create an original pool, and, uh, the Bojani Tour's
[music] water, the water pajan,
and create an original attraction [music] to
invite everyone.
part-time job.
part-time job.  Well, if you ask me what I like to do
, um, I
like making all sorts of things.  Hmm.
Yeah.  I'd
like to create a collection of small items that everyone can use.  [Music] Shop.  The store...
uh, oh, right.  Is it a part-time job?  That's why I
want to help out at the shop.  But then I start
thinking about new products and suggest things like, "How about stocking these kinds of accessories?"
or "How about stocking these kinds of bags?"
or "Why don't we make these kinds of clothes?" and I take
the store on board
.
Wow.  The element I want most.  Yeah.  I agree.
Um,
wow, is that ice?  I want to make the world a little bit cooler with ice
.  It's so hot right now that I can't help but think that way
.  So then the question becomes, what about winter? In
winter, I just stay still and do nothing, and I make
friends with people who have something hot like a flame and let them keep me warm.
Ugh.   I'm not sure
.  Hmm.  The reason why Johnny's Tour has that
connection is because Odette and the other
[music] are quite close and often come up in
conversation, they talk a lot, they are
characters [music] but
personally I thought the relationship or interaction between them that was
interesting was with Mitia, who is, well, a
fan of Johnny's Tour, but the old man is quite aggressive
, he attacks [laughs], he
attacks in a pretty harsh way
, or rather he tests him.
I found that relationship really interesting to portray, so
Mitia has become a
character I'm really interested in.   Let me take a look at the
top 3
.  Top 3.  Hmm.  I chose this one
.  I will make an announcement.  3rd place.  Uh, it's
Ahau.  This character is quite
mysterious.  It seems like they're very
energetic and talk a lot, so I was
thinking that I wouldn't feel lonely on my trip.  But, I wonder what
kind of character this is? Its
style is completely different from the other characters, so it's intriguing and that's why it came in at
number 3
.  Okay, next.  Hmm
.
yes.  2nd place.   This
is Chibi Dorin.  This character is
cute.  The
reason is that I want to take them with me.  Yes, when you eat together, they're
such a kind and cute
character, so I
thought it would be fun and ranked them second.  Next, for the
number one spot, there are
three people.
Okay, I'll announce all three at once.
Dokeitaicho Ph.D.  Well, I couldn't really choose between these three
, but when I received and looked at this document, the
strongest reason I felt I absolutely had to bring these three along was that it seemed very compelling
.  Well, I think there are a lot of other
strong characters,
but this one has a
mysterious aura just from its appearance, and it's so shrouded in shadow that you can barely
see the character's image, and it looks
cool and strong, so I couldn't choose it as number one
.  I thought, "Let's take all three of them with us. With
protection from three directions, we can
travel very safely." [music]
yes.
Um, I just asked one of the staff members
, and I selected my top 3, right?
The number one ranked doctor, the doctor is quite,
uh, scary? Like the final boss, a
character close to the final boss, so I wanted to
choose a character that was safe in all three directions, but well, he is strong, isn't he?  I'm sure they
chose strong characters,
but I also heard earlier that you have to be
a little careful about just one of these three directions
, and I
thought that was quite profound
[laughs].  There are so many
characters that are visually appealing, and I think
all the travelers playing right now are having a
really hard time deciding which one to take with them.
I had a really hard time deciding too
, and now that the
characters from Snezhnaya have also joined the group
, I
think you'll all have an even harder time deciding. But after thinking about it a lot, I
finally decided to take my uncle on my journey
.  thank you
.  Please continue to play with us a lot in the future.   This was
Ioka, playing the role of Boji.  yes.